<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>plod.tv</title>
    <link>https://plod.tv/</link>
    <description>Recent content on plod.tv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:57:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://plod.tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardiff Go 1.8 launch party</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</guid>
      <description>On Febuary the 16th go released it&amp;rsquo;s newest version 1.8. You can read about this release here. I presented at the Cardiff Go meetup group&amp;rsquo;s release party on the 15th. Considering how I am not the greatest speaker in public, it went very well. I was pretty nervous to start, but nerves slowly faded especially when I got to talk about my favourite new features (http2 pushPromice etc). You can see my slides here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Pages and Travis Ci</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/github-pages-and-travis-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 22:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/github-pages-and-travis-ci/</guid>
      <description>I decided that I wanted to move away from self hosted for this website, mostly for resilience (I am often tinkering with thisthat server), though I also wanted to play some with Travis CI to help contributing with more FOSS and playing with different technologies.
I followed the tutorial here paying special attention to the note at the bottom. In a very recent version of hugo there seems to be a problem with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#festive500 2016</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/festive500-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/festive500-2016/</guid>
      <description>What is the festive500?  Rapha creates the finest cycling clothing and accessories in the world. In 2010 we laid down a challenge to our customers; ride 500km on the eight days between Christmas Eve and New Year’s Eve. Since then the Festive 500 has become a tradition. You are joining tens of thousands of riders around the world in getting up off the sofa and onto your bike. Document your adventures to win amazing prizes, and every rider who completes the distance will receive a woven badge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year of the runs </title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/year-of-the-runs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 09:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/year-of-the-runs/</guid>
      <description>2017 will be the year of the runs 🏃💩 for me What does that mean?
Run...To extend or persist, statically or dynamically, through space or time.(intransitive) To extend in time, to last, to continue (usually with a measure phrase).The sale will run for ten days. The contract runs through 2008. The meeting ran late. The book runs 655 pages. The speech runs as follows: …‎... https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/run I am going to run at least 1 mile (though often more than that) every day for 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Go</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 12:27:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate Go Earlier this month I attended Ardan Labs Ultimate Go Training given by Bill Kennedy (https://www.goinggo.net/). Todd McLeod of the Udemy course https://www.udemy.com/learn-how-to-code/ had recommended it, and as I had been working my way through Bill&amp;rsquo;s book Go in Action I was very keen to take my Go to the next level.
The course was hosted at Hailo&amp;rsquo;s HQ in central London. Big shout out to them for hosting it, and for the excellent facilities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Euler</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 10:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</guid>
      <description>So I decided to do the projects on Project Euler to help with my Go learning (and to get my maths head working again), I&amp;rsquo;d forgotten how much fun the problems were.
What is Project Euler?
 Project Euler is a series of challenging mathematical/computer programming problems that will require more than just mathematical insights to solve. Although mathematics will help you arrive at elegant and efficient methods, the use of a computer and programming skills will be required to solve most problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing goSwitchBackup</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</guid>
      <description>goSwitchBackup is Go program I wrote, to automate the backing up of Cisco switches over SSH for the network boys in work. It essentially SSHs (can you use it like a verb like that?) into an IP (Which should be the address of a Cisco switch) using the password, once it receives the prompt character it trys to escalate privileges using: enable Once it sees the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; character it then tries to run the backup command: copy running-config tftpIt will then give the TFTP server address used when the program was invoked, and name the file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audax: Malmesbury Mash 2016</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/malmesbury-mash-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 08:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/malmesbury-mash-2016/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday gone, I rode my 200km Audax of the month of February &amp;ldquo;Malmesbury Mash&amp;rdquo;. I try to ride at least a 200km every month of the year to achieve the Audax UK award Randonneur Round the Year. Last year on my 12th successive month on the ride to claim this award, I managed to break my collar bone, but that&amp;rsquo;s another story entirely.
Things did not start well for the preparation for this ride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple site free ssl with http2 nginx</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/multiple-site-free-ssl-http2-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/multiple-site-free-ssl-http2-nginx/</guid>
      <description>There still exists this myth that you require a single IP address per vhost for an ssl certificate. It was perpetuated because the encryption handshake used to happen before the resource required could be ascertained, thanks to some pretty serious security vulnerabilites SSL itself is pretty much a dead duck and the modern TLS has superceded it. One of the great things about TLS is SNI:
 Server Name Indication (SNI) is an extension to the TLS computer networking protocol[1] by which a client indicates which hostname it is attempting to connect to at the start of the handshaking process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a hugo based website on ubuntu then auto deploy using gogs&#39; webhooks</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/setting-up-hugo-git-auto-deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 12:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/setting-up-hugo-git-auto-deploy/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo?  Hugo is a static HTML and CSS website generator written in Go. It is optimized for speed, easy use and configurability. Hugo takes a directory with content and templates and renders them into a full HTML website.
Hugo relies on Markdown files with front matter for meta data. And you can run Hugo from any directory. This works well for shared hosts and other systems where you don’t have a privileged account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 12:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description> This is my first post on the site. I hope that you like it!
Welcome Function Here is a little Golang function to welcome you:
package main import &#34;fmt&#34; func main() { fmt.Println(&#34;Sut mae, byd!&#34;) } </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>