<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Driven Design on plod.tv</title>
    <link>https://plod.tv/tags/data-driven-design/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Driven Design on plod.tv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://plod.tv/tags/data-driven-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Go</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 12:27:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ultimate-go&#34;&gt;Ultimate Go&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month I attended &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ardanlabs.com/&#34;&gt;Ardan Labs&lt;/a&gt; Ultimate Go Training given by Bill Kennedy (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goinggo.net/&#34;&gt;https://www.goinggo.net/&lt;/a&gt;). Todd McLeod of the Udemy course &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/learn-how-to-code/&#34;&gt;https://www.udemy.com/learn-how-to-code/&lt;/a&gt; had recommended it, and as I had been working my way through Bill&amp;rsquo;s book &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.manning.com/books/go-in-action&#34;&gt;Go in Action&lt;/a&gt; I was very keen to take my Go to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The course was hosted at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hailoapp.com/&#34;&gt;Hailo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s HQ in central London. Big shout out to them for hosting it, and for the excellent facilities! I took the whole family up to Cambridge to stay with friends, and then commuted into central London each day for the course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bill is a very passionate guy and I think he could get motivate excitement in computer programming and advanced concepts in anybody. I learnt a lot of things that I&amp;rsquo;d not put much thought into, and some anti patterns that I thought I&amp;rsquo;d been doing to improve things but had essentially been slowing things down. You can get a background idea about the course from it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ardanlabs/gotraining/tree/master/courses/ultimate&#34;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;, or it is worth listening to this weeks &lt;a href=&#34;https://changelog.com/gotime-6/&#34;&gt;Go Time&lt;/a&gt; podcast where you can hear Bill talk about a few of the topics of the course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thoroughly reccomend anybody no matter what level you are at to give the training a go (pardon the pun) Bill seems to be everywhere all the time, so I&amp;rsquo;m sure you can fit it in somewhere! Oh and he signed my Go in Action book 😁!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>