<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Go on plod.tv</title>
    <link>https://plod.tv/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Go on plod.tv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:57:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://plod.tv/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardiff Go 1.8 launch party</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</guid>
      <description>On Febuary the 16th go released it&amp;rsquo;s newest version 1.8. You can read about this release here. I presented at the Cardiff Go meetup group&amp;rsquo;s release party on the 15th. Considering how I am not the greatest speaker in public, it went very well. I was pretty nervous to start, but nerves slowly faded especially when I got to talk about my favourite new features (http2 pushPromice etc). You can see my slides here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Go</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 12:27:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate Go Earlier this month I attended Ardan Labs Ultimate Go Training given by Bill Kennedy (https://www.goinggo.net/). Todd McLeod of the Udemy course https://www.udemy.com/learn-how-to-code/ had recommended it, and as I had been working my way through Bill&amp;rsquo;s book Go in Action I was very keen to take my Go to the next level.
The course was hosted at Hailo&amp;rsquo;s HQ in central London. Big shout out to them for hosting it, and for the excellent facilities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Euler</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 10:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</guid>
      <description>So I decided to do the projects on Project Euler to help with my Go learning (and to get my maths head working again), I&amp;rsquo;d forgotten how much fun the problems were.
What is Project Euler?
 Project Euler is a series of challenging mathematical/computer programming problems that will require more than just mathematical insights to solve. Although mathematics will help you arrive at elegant and efficient methods, the use of a computer and programming skills will be required to solve most problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing goSwitchBackup</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</guid>
      <description>goSwitchBackup is Go program I wrote, to automate the backing up of Cisco switches over SSH for the network boys in work. It essentially SSHs (can you use it like a verb like that?) into an IP (Which should be the address of a Cisco switch) using the password, once it receives the prompt character it trys to escalate privileges using: enable Once it sees the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; character it then tries to run the backup command: copy running-config tftpIt will then give the TFTP server address used when the program was invoked, and name the file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a hugo based website on ubuntu then auto deploy using gogs&#39; webhooks</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/setting-up-hugo-git-auto-deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 12:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/setting-up-hugo-git-auto-deploy/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo?  Hugo is a static HTML and CSS website generator written in Go. It is optimized for speed, easy use and configurability. Hugo takes a directory with content and templates and renders them into a full HTML website.
Hugo relies on Markdown files with front matter for meta data. And you can run Hugo from any directory. This works well for shared hosts and other systems where you don’t have a privileged account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 12:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description> This is my first post on the site. I hope that you like it!
Welcome Function Here is a little Golang function to welcome you:
package main import &#34;fmt&#34; func main() { fmt.Println(&#34;Sut mae, byd!&#34;) } </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>