<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on plod.tv</title>
    <link>https://plod.tv/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on plod.tv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:02:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://plod.tv/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WinOps 2018</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/winops-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:02:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/winops-2018/</guid>
      <description>As part of my job with DevOpsGroup I&#39;ve been doing more and more work with my clients in the windows space, as a result I got the opportunity to attend WinOps 2018 last november.
So what is WinOps?  WinOps (a portmanteau of &amp;ldquo;Windows&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo;) is a term used referring to the cultural movement of DevOps practices for a Microsoft-centric view. It emphasizes the use of the cloud, automation and integrating development and IT operations into one fluid method on the Windows platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDD Wales 2018</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/ddd-wales-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/ddd-wales-2018/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday I attended Developer Developer Developer Wales with Nigel, Dai, Pete and we bumped into James Alfie.
 The UK&#39;s premier FREE Developer conference is coming to Wales! Since its inception in 2005, DDD has spread across the UK and throughout other parts of the world, as far afield as Melbourne and Perth. This time though it is heading to Swansea!
DDD is a free one day technical event for developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardiff Go 1.8 launch party</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/go-1.8-launch-party/</guid>
      <description>On Febuary the 16th go released it&#39;s newest version 1.8. You can read about this release here. I presented at the Cardiff Go meetup group&#39;s release party on the 15th. Considering how I am not the greatest speaker in public, it went very well. I was pretty nervous to start, but nerves slowly faded especially when I got to talk about my favourite new features (http2 pushPromice etc). You can see my slides here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year of the runs </title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/year-of-the-runs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 09:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/year-of-the-runs/</guid>
      <description>2017 will be the year of the runs 🏃💩 for me What does that mean?
I am going to run at least 1 mile (though often more than that) every day for 2017. I am not going to have just a run of runs I am hoping to:I will/have started some of these runs (streaks) before 2017 but the important pledge is that from the 1stof January = until the 31stof December I will have an unbroken run of these things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Go</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 12:27:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/ultimate-go/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate Go Earlier this month I attended Ardan Labs Ultimate Go Training given by Bill Kennedy (https://www.goinggo.net/). Todd McLeod of the Udemy course https://www.udemy.com/learn-how-to-code/ had recommended it, and as I had been working my way through Bill&#39;s book Go in Action I was very keen to take my Go to the next level.
The course was hosted at Hailo&amp;lsquo;s HQ in central London. Big shout out to them for hosting it, and for the excellent facilities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Euler</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 10:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/project-euler/</guid>
      <description>So I decided to do the projects on Project Euler to help with my Go learning (and to get my maths head working again), I&#39;d forgotten how much fun the problems were.
What is Project Euler?
 Project Euler is a series of challenging mathematical/computer programming problems that will require more than just mathematical insights to solve. Although mathematics will help you arrive at elegant and efficient methods, the use of a computer and programming skills will be required to solve most problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing goSwitchBackup</title>
      <link>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://plod.tv/post/announcing-goswitchbackup/</guid>
      <description>goSwitchBackup is Go program I wrote, to automate the backing up of Cisco switches over SSH for the network boys in work. It essentially SSHs (can you use it like a verb like that?) into an IP (Which should be the address of a Cisco switch) using the password, once it receives the prompt character it trys to escalate privileges using: enable Once it sees the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; character it then tries to run the backup command: copy running-config tftpIt will then give the TFTP server address used when the program was invoked, and name the file:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>